Good evening everyone!
It's time for JOSEO TV!
It's started!
It is the theme song of the drama, Koujouji Koi Laundry 2!
Thank you again!
Everyone, please check out the mina SHOW!
It's Sumasubance, so I'll put it on it.
We are going to play cute Jenga today!
Anyway, just be cute!
Anyway, we will play Jenga with cuteness!
Let's play Jenga with love!
There will be a penalty game, too.
Let's be cute, but don't beat them!
Let's do our best!
Order, Janken poi!
Look at us!
For us to shake!
Oh, we're rocking!
We have to try not to shake too much.
All right, first one is goo, then rock, paper, scissors!
Then, rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper scissors!
That's just plain scary, Hal.
I'm getting a little scared, Hal.
My heart is pounding!
Then don't shake it!
Twenty-two times.
I can't get out of this one at all.
What about the one you picked?
Can't I change it?
I can't pull it out at all.
Can I change it?
You can change it.
It's stuck! I can't pull it off at all.
Well, make it pretty!
It doesn't pull out at all! I don't know.
I don't like the weight.
It's totally stuck!
Whoa! That's good, isn't it?
Nice!
Nice pull!
It's new, so it's not stuck, is it?
Stuck?
It's stuck.
Just take at least one step forward in the middle.
I'm surprised you can't pull it out where it looks like it's going to fall out.
Oh, really?
Okay, here we go.
I'm sorry, it's... it's... it's...
It's so tight.
You can't pull it off.
Yeah, that's good.
You look good. I'm doing good.
Good luck. Now.
Come on! Take a risk!
I'll do my best.
I don't mind taking a shot once in a while.
What? I don't even look like him.
You're so cute, aren't you? You made a sound.
Let's do it this way.
Ohhh...
Where?Where?
I don't see him.
Cute wind god formed.
Peace.
Oh, my God, he's so cute!
Put it on your phone for now.
I found it!
It shakes when you walk on it.
Okay, okay.
I'm gonna go to the middle of the street, just like that.
Activity, Irajulah.
Oh!
You want to go there?
There you go.
Look! Look at that!
Look at that!
It's so good!
Is it big?
It's pretty small.
That's amazing!
That's quite a game you've got there.
Oh, man!
Okay, round two, MOHARU!
Round two!
Indescribable green peppers!
Muzukasha piman!
I haven't seen him at all!
I found it!
You were aiming for it?
Mm-hmm.
I found it.
Yuck.
Here you go.
There you go.
Yay.
Come on.
The moment your turn is over...
Wow!
You're early.
Soooo...
The balance is getting better and better
Here you go.
I'm thrilled for you.
It's pretty heavy, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
What if we twist it?
Around here?
This might be a good place.
Hmm.
What?
Yeah, I think you're right.
I shouldn't have said that earlier.
It's getting more and more difficult.
First place.
It's good!
Yum!
It's so good!
It's good.
GoodYou're good.
You have to look pretty, don't you?
Yes, ma'am.
You're so cute.
Oh! Oh, that's funny!
Oh!
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my gosh! Is now a good time?
Now!
It's really coming through.
Yeah!
Oh! It's working!
Wow!
Is it okay?
It's working!
Oh, it's coming out!
That's good!
I can do it!
Wow, I love it!
Oh, my God!
Oh, man! There's so many!
Oh!
Yeah!
Wow! I've got a head and legs!
Whoa! I've got a head and legs!
I can do it! I can do it!
Oh, my gosh!
Wow!
It's so tight!
Isn't he cute?
It's so good.
That's great, that's great, that's great, that's great.
It's so tight.
You do it.
That's great.
Oh, wow.
The pressure's on.
That's not good.
That's a good three rounds.
Not so bad, huh? This one.
That's pretty good.
Round three.
Did you find it?
Looks pretty tight.
We're running out of room in the middle.
Did you find it?
It's pretty hard to find, Chu.
Chu.
Oh, did you find the rock?
Oh, my God.
That feels good.
It's pretty hard to find, Chew.
Looks like we'll get through this with a kiss.
Uh-oh.
Oh, did you find it?
Oh, you found it?
You found it.
You found it. You found the kiss.
You found it.I found it... the chew.
Oh, but...
But...
Scary, scary, scary, scary, scary.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Oh, my gosh.
Ew, scary
I have a bad feeling
I'm shaking.
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Are you serious?
For real?
I found it!
Mwah!
Is this it?
This one?
Mwah!
It's shaking like this.
Eh, kanmin
Good!
Good job!
You're good!
You've got it!
Everyone!
How do you feel now?
That's great!
Feels good!
Feels good.
Macho, come here, come here.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Cute!
It doesn't move at all.
You don't think he's going to pull two out?
It's not good to pull two out.
All these two out...
Oh! Oh, up.
Huh! We're out.
Gentlemen.
When I put it down, you give me your hand.
Okay, okay.
Wow! That's amazing!
That's so cute.
Oh, my God! That's amazing!
Oh, my God.
It's so cute!
Oh! Oh! You're good! Are you serious?
I'm serious!
Do you want to spin around a little?
Wasn't that cute? Now!
Ha-ha-ha!
Oh, what do I do?
I had to make a pretty face.
Oh, that's good!
Oh, my goodness!
Oh, my goodness. Oh, my goodness.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
It's going on.
That's good!
That's great!
Safe safe safe safe
Oh, yeah.Oh, really?
Wow!
I'm so excited.
There's your cereal.
Oh!
It's like an art object.
Oh, my God.
You're like an artist.
Oh!
Safe.
Oh, my God.
That's so good.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
Did it work?
I found it.
What?
You're so good, guys.
I didn't think it would last this long.
I think I'm gonna catch my breath.
How many laps?
This is lap four.
I can't find it.
What?
No way. Here?
Here?
Oh, great, great, great.
It's got a lot of weight.
Ohhh...
Ew.
Oh no!
Oh no, I don't want it to come around!
It's amazing!
It won't come around!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
But I just pulled a pretty good position.
Oh!
Hey, you know, they said it's supposed to be done in about three or four weeks.
Wow, seriously?
Seriously?
Mach.
Mach?
Oh, man.
I was at the bottom.
Yahveh.
Yuka has a great body.
Amazing.
You're so beautiful!
Yuka, try going with your feet!
Good, good!
So beautiful!
Okay, wait for me.
If you fall down with this poof, it's Julia's shot.
Wait a minute.
She's a magician.
First time.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, it's working.
Good, good, good.
I think I was pretty aggressive.
I love it when we're in a group.It's so good when it's a group.
It's good.
It's pretty good, but...
Oh!
What? I got it.
I got it.
That's great.
But it's heavy.
Oh, really?
It's good.
It's amazing.
That's great.
Not quite.
Excuse me. One more time.
Okay, okay.
I'll walk along the wall.
Okay, let's go.
No, no, no, no.
It's heavy. It's heavy. It's heavy.
Oh, my God.
It's so cute.
Can we go here?
Oh, no.
The top part comes out the other way?
Is it?
Oh, I really don't think I can go.
Okay, here we go.
Does it weigh anything?
Yeah, it does.
It hurts.
I don't think I can do this.
Operation Tune Tune Tune Tune.
It's stuck.
Click.
Hold on.
I don't think we should go in there.
I think we can go now.
This is the only way to go.
Pretty face.
I remember now.
See you next time.
Oh! I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it.
Oh! I got it!
No, just a little more.
That's not good enough.
Oh, no!
Oh! Yes!
Oh! Yeah!
Good job!
Gah!
Yeah!
Okay!
Whoa!
Aah! Chokers all around!
New talent.
You don't have one, do you?
Maybe not.
We're the only ones who depend on us now.There is only one person we can count on anymore.
Tasai Open
Oh!
There he is.
I think I can make it.
But it's a little heavy.
It's a little heavy.
Oh!
It's just this side.
It's heavy.
Like this.
It's too good.
Hang in there.
I think I can do it.
A little lower.
Oh!
Real shoes.
I'm nervous too
They're heavy.
They look pretty heavy.
This shit.
On the contrary, it's awesome.
This is shit.
It's art.
Power to the people!
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Wow!
I made it!
That's great.
That's pretty good.
Why don't you just finish what you started?
You can't do this, can you?
I'm going over the edge.
I mean, just a little more touch of this.
I'm gonna get wet.
Oh, come on!
Make a pretty face.
Good!
I can't do it anymore.
You're not gonna make it, are you?
Aah! No! No!
Why, why, why, why?
Stop it!
Aaah!
Aaah! No!
Stop it! Stop it!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm coming out.
Whoa.
Oh, it's coming around.
It's coming around!It's coming around.
But no, no, no, no.
It's okay.
Let's be frank.
Let's do it now.
I can finish, can't I?
Oh, wow.
That's great.
Wow, that's amazing.
Hey, isn't it amazing?
Wow.
Oh!
Oh... oh!
Huh?
No, that looks good.
That looks good.
It's both nice and it's nice.
Okay, wait a minute.
Gachi-gachi, can you do Jenka?
Oh, my gosh.
That's great.
Subtle.
It's hard.
Oh, yeah.
It's like that action you just saw.
Wow.
I can do it!
I feel like it's finally here.
I feel like I'm gonna beat him.
There's always the next Julian.
Next time.
I'm counting on you.
I'm nervous.
I don't think I'm going to make it.
But if you're done with this...
Don't shake it.
Like this.
I don't know...
It's amazing.
I felt like Jenga was distorted.
Let's take all the pictures without shaking them.
Smile!
Go for it!
You're too cute.
Is this okay?
Oh, there's so many chains.
So cute.
I like the camera.
Oh, yeah.
Oh!
Nice!
Oh, my gosh!
That's great!
You're a pear! You're gonna knock it over!
That bad?
I'm so nervous!
Oh, my God!
No way.
It's heavy. All of it.
It's heavy.Heavy.
Is she pretty?
Face.
Two, right?
Are you going down?
But, you know, it's not there.
I don't have a place.
You'll find a place.
What?
Lena, wait a minute.
Here...
Feet. Feet.
Amazing!
That's great!
I got it! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
Yikes!
Cha-ching!
I saw you move it earlier.
Cute?
I kind of forgot.
You have to go half berserk.
What the hell?
Yuki-chan, how long are your arms?
Oh, no, no, no, no...
Oh, my God!
Oh, here it comes!
You're so cute!
I have to make a cute face.
I'm shaking a little.
Wait a minute. Can you do this?
It's coming. It's coming.
It's coming.
Oh, my God.
That's amazing.
It's personality recognition.
It's really...
You can do that for half an hour.
I can see it.
It's not that great.
You know, first game.
I'm gonna hoof it, and if I don't hit it, I'm gonna lose it.
There's something on the right side.
What corner?
That's pretty awesome.
I don't think I've ever been on a corner like this before.
Wow!
That's amazing!
Wow, that's amazing.
That's a game I could play forever.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You can't do this anymore.
It's totally fine.
I think we can do it.
What, is this forever?
No?
How long?
Dozens.
Oh, my God!
I don't think so.I don't think so.
I'm scared.
Wait, that's too tight.
Too tight!
It's too tight!
I'm scared.
Oh! Oh, you can do it!
Oh!
You can do it!
I'm scared.
Well, you won't find anything like that there.
No, there really isn't.
Oh, wow.
I can do it.
I'm scared.
My hands are so sweaty.
Yuck.
But, but...
A-ha-ha!
Aaaaah!
A dead man...
A dead man.
Seep, seep, seep.
Oh, my heart
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
The next one's in trouble.
That's gonna be tough.
Good job, guys.
You guys are so cool.
I don't think I can do this anymore.
My hands are sweating.
You're funny. Hiyori's a genius.
Hiyori's a genius!
This is seriously awesome!
Oh, my God!
Here it comes!
It's here!
For real?
Oh my god.
Oh my god!
Oh, my god.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
This is amazing.
You can do that much?
I can't do it.
I mean, it's amazing, but it's really...
Oh, my God.
It's going to be personalized.
It's about time.
Is he really gone?
He's gone!
Oh, man, we can ride now.
We can ride now!
And you know, when we're riding, we're not riding straight, so it's getting more and more skewed.
LOL!
This is amazing!
Because I turned it a lot, that turn I just made.
Oh, wow!
I can do it.I'm ready.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Downswing.
You know, that's really distorted.
It's working.
I think I'm gonna lose it.
It's gone
It's so loose
Very loose
George, you should put that in there.
It's gone, isn't it?
I mean, you can't even touch it. You can't even see it.
It's gone.
Oh, here you go.
What?
It's gone.
It's really gone!
It's okay, sweetie. It's okay.
Come on!
You'll be fine.
Seriously, there's no room.
I can't! No! No! No!
Happy!
What about up there?
Wait a minute, the top's stuck.
Oh, I'm gonna take this down.
There's a penalty for going this far.
And the second one from the top.
Oh, you couldn't do it? I touched it.
Right here?
Oh, yes.
I can't do it.
I can't. I can't.
But you're right. It's got a lot of weight directly on it.
And down there, too.
We're only about three or four weeks along.
Oh, my God.
But if you do this...
But if you do it this way... it's on this side.
Oh, you're right.
You can't do it this way.
Everything is on this side.
If I pull it out, it's going to fall over.
It's true.
You know what I mean? That's what I'm trying to say.
But this is the only way it's going to work.
I was going to go 12 times from the bottom.
It didn't work here either.
Wait, really?
But no, I don't want to play the penalty game.
Let's do it together.
I can't do it. I can't do it. I can't do it.
I know, right?
What do we do?
But, you know, we can't do it this way.
Can't we just do it this way?
No?
Hey, guys.
Put it over here.Put it over here.
This one's not in such a relatively good place.
We're gonna have to pull this out.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no.
If we pull this out, we'll be left with...
It's gone.
What?
But it's stuck!
It's so heavy.
If I pull it out, it'll fall on that side.
But it's the only way to pull it out.
It's the only way to pull it out.
Oh, God.
I can hear my heart beating like this because I'm so scared.
Everybody hold still.
That's the hardest part.
I think I'm gonna collapse if you don't pull it out.
If you pull it out, you're gonna fall over.
Oh, my God!
You sure?
He pulled it out!
Rick!
Seriously?
George, keep up the good work!
Come on, George!
I have to touch the plate.
George's concentration.
Yeah.
I don't think he's coming around.
Oh, no.
I'm not getting any better.
That's great!
If Stalags had a Jänger event, it would be the best!
One hour.
One hour!
Oh!
Really?
Oh, yeah?
We have to do this together.
They're here.
He came shopping.
This is someone's room.
Like a bird.
I think I'm going to get a hunchback.
I'm gonna get an obstacle.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Okay? Hey, guys.
Did he just say that to you with such a pretty face?
All I can do is say yes.
Good night, sweetie.
Good night.
There you go. There you go.
Hang in there.
I'm not gonna run out of steam.
Oh! He's coming around back!
Oh, my gosh!Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my gosh!
I can do it! I can do it! Go for it!
Come on, Axia!
You can do it!
You can do it! You can do it!
I believe in you!
Aki-chan's challenge has come this far!
Okay!
Watch out!
Oh, no! Come on!
Come on!
Sooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo...
Soot, soot, soot.
Sooooo...
Oh, no!
Hang in there.
Oh, I think it's coming!
Here.
Oh!
I'm hungry.
Aaaaah!
Ahhh...
Tummy
Aaaaahhh!
Aki-chan wins!
Amazing!
You're going up so high!
Aki-chan is good, too!
I didn't know it could go on like this!
Amazing!
I'm surprised!
I didn't know it could go on like this!
That's amazing!
I can't help it if you play the penalty game, Aki-chan!
I want to play the penalty game!
You're so cute! Nice punishment game!
You're so cute! Please give me a lot!
Can I?
Please tell me I'm cute!
Thank you!
The first one!
Cute!
The second one!
The third one!
Cute!
The fourth one.
Cute.
Cute!
The sixth one.
Cute and cute!
And a half!
Cute!
Cute 2
Cute!Cute.
Two more.
Three more.
Cute!
Cute.
Two more.
Only 2 more to wear?
Cute.
One more.
It's so cute!
Okay, cute!
Bye bye!
Thank you very much!
I don't know why, but when I smile, it sure makes the world seem to glow.
I can turn my umbrella around and take it easy because otherwise I wouldn't be able to walk.
I'm sure somewhere someone's crying, somewhere I'll get wet again, somewhere I won't get cold.
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying because I want to share just a little bit of my feelings with them
I want to share just a little bit of my feelings with you, so I'll go wherever you take me
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for yesterday After the rain, the cityscape turns color
On the canvas of my broken heart, a piece of the future is painted, guiding me along
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for yesterday After the rain, the streets are turning colors
Now I can tell you the reason for my tears
Whenever you're lost, just remember
I'll smile even when it's raining
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
The town after the rain, the waves are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny day, making puddles of sound
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye Goodbye to Yesterday's Me
The city after the rain, the waves are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny day, spilling clouds of tears
I'll wear a rainbow dress
Lalala...
Please subscribe to our channel!